When I throw a jab or a straight, it always lands
But when I'm aiming for your heart, I miss every time
Parallel, zigzagging, awkward, incoherent
When you look my way and move closer to me
I know it doesn't mean the same thing for you
But I wish we could stay like this forever
My changing feelings are driving me crazy
The moment you turn to face me, take that! Telepathy
If only we could feel the same thing
I want to kick this pesky subtlety away
I want to know everything, I want to know everything
I can't fool you forever
I can't keep this hidden
I want to shout out my secret, AHHH
Take that! Telepathy
Te-te-te-telepathy
Telepathy
Goodbye, Best Friend
"Goodbye, Best Friend."
Cultural Festival
Uenomizu High School
I can't wait to see Tomo and
the other kids in the play.
Yes!
I'm so glad I got to meet Tomo-chan's
and Misuzu-chan's moms.
I don't think I'd be able to hold
myself back if I was alone.
I'll be counting on you both!
To do what, now?
Never thought I'd see you at
a cultural festival, though.
I guess even you love
your own daughter, huh?
She told me there wouldn't be
a cultural festival this year.
Huh? Why would she lie about that?
I guess she really didn't want me seeing her.
Which is why I came... to film it.
It's what she gets for lying to her mother.
She really can't just be honest and say she
wants to film her daughter's performance?
Once upon a time, in a land far away,
there lived a young girl.
Her name was Cinderella.
Her stepmother and stepsisters
were very mean to her.
They forced her to do housework
every single day without rest.
Poor, pitiful Cinderella!
Sob, sob. Sob, sob. Sob, sob.
I wouldn't call her "pitiful"...
She looks like she's out for blood.
Have you finished the cleaning, Cinderella?
Carol-chan!
This is what you wanted us for?!
Oh, I wish I could go to the ball, too.
I want to dance in a beautiful dress,
like Mother and my sisters!
Oh?
No one's realized that he's there.
He's completely concealed his presence
and melted into the scenery.
He is most definitely a tree!
Thank you, everyone,
for coming to see me today.
What a beautiful lady you are.
Would you dance with me?
I will.
Tomo...
You really are...
a prince to the core.
But I bet you wish you could be a
princess sometimes, too, right?
I swear...
Just try being the one who has
to deal with you all the time.
I was the one who instilled in you
the sort of values that made you
think you'd rather be a princess.
It's not how you really feel.
But all of it is who you are, including that.
I've finally found you,
owner of the glass slipper.
Will you marry me?
Congratulations, Cinderella!
I'm so upset, but congratulations!
Congratulations!
Huh?!
You're supposed to be furious about this.
Congrats, Cinderella! I wish you happiness!
Congratulations!
What's going on?
I mean, I guess it's all good.
We've been through a lot,
but it was fun, huh?
That's true.
This wasn't such a bad punishment.
We Ain't Right
Yeah! We pulled it off!
You did great, Tomo.
Wanna walk around the festival with me?
Oh... Sure, but...
You can take that thing off now.
Maid Café
W-Welcome, master!
Th-This cake is our top recommendation.
Like, on the house!
Wow, really?
Way to go, Tomo.
Here.
The coffee you ordered.
Drink it and, like, get the hell outta here.
Huh?
Welcome Home, Master
Haunted House
Hey, relax! The ghost is gone!
Damn it!
How did I lose all three rounds?!
Heh! Try challenging me
again in about ten years!
We're going one more round
once we're done eating!
I won't lose this time!
Sounds fun! I accept!
Yeah, being with him is still a total blast!
But I'm thinking of ending what we have.
Is that really what I want?
Isn't this fun, Ko-chan?
Yeah...
Aizawa-san! Please dance with me!
And then me!
Me, too! Me, too!
Whoa, hang—
Tomo... You wanna dance with me?
Huh?! W-Well, sure, I guess...
Wh-What?! Stop clapping!
What am I expecting will happen
if I stand around here?
Hey, Misuzu-chan. Do you
wanna dance with me?
What? Didn't you hear me?
They both have someone to spend
the festival after-party with.
They don't have time to waste on m—
Sorry. Have you been waiting?
I suppose I should thank you.
So thanks.
Huh? For what?
Did I do something?
Don't play dumb with me.
You got me the Cinderella role so
I'd make up with Tomo, didn't you?
You were fighting?
Huh?
This is all I was after.
Give me that! I'm deleting it!
No!
Th-This is more embarrassing than I expected.
Yeah... it is.
Never thought you'd ask me to dance.
I know you were just asking as a friend,
but y'know, if you ask me like
that in front of people,
they might get the wrong idea.
It's not... wrong.
Huh?
They wouldn't be wrong.
Huh? Tomo-chan?
Tomo?
It's cold...
Morning, Jun!
Don't get all shriveled up just 'cause it's cold!
Get those spirits up and let's go!
Tomo's been like this ever since that day.
At a glance, she just seems
super energetic, but...
So then, y'know what Misuzu did?
Hey, Tomo, about the after-party...
O-Oh, yeah! I just remembered I need to
get to school early to do something!
Should I take this as a rejection?
Morning, Misuzu-chan!
Good morning.
Look at this, Tomo-chan! I'm hugging her,
and she's not getting mad!
It's a miracle!
Well, Misuzu really hates being cold.
You must be warming her up by hugging her.
I wish it'd stay winter forever!
Hey, where's Jun-kun?
He didn't come with you today?
Huh? O-Oh, yeah...
He came with me part of the
way, b-but stuff happened...
Hey, Tomo-chan, did something happen
between you two at the cultural festival?
Huh?! B-Between me and Jun?!
N-No, nothing at all! So much nothing
that it's killing me, actually!
Something did happen.
I knew it.
Junichiro probably said something that
amounted to confessing his feelings,
and she chose to run away from him.
Why, though? Their feelings
were finally mutual.
Why? I mean...
Morning, Jun-kun.
Oh, hey.
Is something wrong?
The thing is... there's someone I like.
Wait, are you saying it's...
It's Tomo.
What'd you do that for?
S-Sorry! I was just so happy,
I couldn't stop myself!
So... what do you think I should do?
Well...
If I told you there was a good way
to handle it, would you do it?
I think the best thing you can do is
tell her straight-up that you like her.
I think that's the thing that'll
work best for you two.
Wait, did I sound kinda patronizing there?
No.
Thank you for the advice.
No, it was nothing!
To be honest, I'm not really in any
position to give anyone love advice.
I'm only going out with Carol now
because someone set the stage for me.
I didn't do any of the work on my own.
So now that she's accepted me
even knowing that's how I am,
I want to get all the feelings across
to her that I never could before.
Telling someone you like
them isn't easy to do.
It's really scary, even.
So let's both give it our all.
Right.
I've decided what to do.
I'm going to tell her how I feel up-front.
But there are some steps I need to take first.
Got a minute to talk, Gundo?
Gundo...
Sorry. I'm in love with Tomo.
Huh?
What does that have to do with me?
Just... sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
I'm pretty sure, ever since
you and I went out...
No, even before that, I already loved her.
So I realize it's selfish of me
to tell you I love her now.
Wait... Are you saying that's why you
couldn't be more proactive with Tomo?
That's not all of it, but...
I can't believe he was
still worried about me.
I swear, he's such a...
Hey, you okay? Does your head hurt?
Don't get cocky!
Do you think our brief relationship
happened at your discretion?
I picked it up and I threw it away!
It was my mistake!
A huge mistake.
If you're being considerate of me,
forget about it right now.
Got it?
Y-Yeah...
Thanks.
Huh? I didn't do anything to be thanked for.
No, not just for today.
You've always been pretty good at
looking out for others, y'know?
It's just a feeling,
but I'm pretty sure I only made
it to this point because of you.
Am I wrong?
I swear. He and Tomo both...
I disagree.
Thanks for hearing me out.
Let's head back to class.
Wait.
Tell me one last thing.
Was I...
your first love?
F-First love?!
No... you weren't.
I see. So I wasn't your first, then.
Incidentally, I've never
been in love with anyone.
Oh, is that so?!
I really can't stand you!
What's this?
Letter of Challenge
Aizawa Tomo,
I challenge you to a duel.
Wait for me on the rooftop today after school.
A challenge letter?!
Yo! What idiot tried to
pick a fight with me?!
J-Jun?! You tricked me!
Yep.
I didn't think you'd actually
fall for it, though.
It's all over! I can't get away!
Tomo...
Please...
Please hit me!
Wha?!
And why do I have to hit you?
Because I deserve to be hit.
What the hell?!
I don't have any reason to...
Right after we started high school,
when we were standing
under those cherry trees,
you told me you loved me.
I love you, Jun!
Huh?
You didn't just mean "as a friend," did you?
You realized I was confessing to you?
Yeah.
You knew how I felt?
That's right.
And you knew...
that I was trying so hard to
be more girly just for you...
and you were just ignoring it?!
You were trying to be more girly... for me?
S-Sorry... I didn't know about tha—
Ow...
I hit him.
I don't even have any right to hit him.
I can understand wanting to
run away painfully well.
Jun must have been afraid, too.
But right now, he's looking right
at me and not running away.
I'm the one running away now!
Wait!
I know your feelings might
have changed by now.
But even if they have, I still...
love you!
Shut up, dumbass!
Dumbass?!
Dumbass...
I blew it!
So then you called him a
dumbass and ran away, huh?
I mean... I just freaked out!
"Dumbass" was just mean, though.
Quit rubbing salt in the wound!
You know you love each other now.
You should just go out.
What does "going out" even mean?
Huh?
What makes it different
from the way we are now?
How are Jun and I supposed to be?
Is everything just gonna work out,
even though I don't understand anything?
What if I screw it up?
Tomo...
You've always called me your best friend,
but this is the first time we've
really faced each other head-on.
Tomo...
I want you to listen carefully
to what I'm about to tell you.
Huh?
Because I'm pretty sure I'll
only be able to say it once.
I'm sorry.
What's going on between you and
Junichiro now is all my fault.
Huh? No way! I should be thanking you for—
You shouldn't.
There was never any need to force
yourself to be more girly.
You were just fine the way you were.
No one ever... wanted you to change.
M-Misu—
A-A-Are you... crying?!
I am not.
Sorry, Misuzu.
I guess I kinda backed you into a corner.
I put myself in a corner. That's all.
But more importantly...
Just go to him and settle all this.
Like you always do. Right?
Misuzu...
I'm so glad you're my best friend!
Yeah, yeah.
Love sure is nice.
With the one you love, you can
be stubborn, cry, throw a fit...
And they'll understand that
that's just the way it goes.
My feelings are so incomprehensible,
no one would ever understand them.
I don't think it matters whether
someone's a friend or a love interest.
It's okay to have lots of
different types of love.
You and I are just friends,
but I still want to kiss you.
Get off me.
Jun!
Tomo?
Sorry about before! I won't run away again!
So just give me one more... one more chance!
I just want to make sure I understood.
So you really... l-love me?
Yes, I do!
Really?!
Yes!
Really for real?!
Yes, for real!
Jun really, actually loves me!
As a man... and he loves me as a girl!
I never thought this day would come!
It feels like a dream!
But that also means...
You're really sure about that?
Huh?
After today, you and I might
not be best buds anymore.
You're okay with that?
Not best buds anymore? Why?
Are you saying you don't wanna...
g-go out with me?!
I'm not saying that!
So we can't stay best buds, then, can we?!
I don't wanna quit that, either!
How selfish can you be?!
What do you want us to be, then?!
Well, I mean...
For example...
Ready... go!
Huh?!
Hey! Wait up, damn it!
I still can't beat you, huh?
Wh-Why the hell did you suddenly take off?
This is what I want.
This is the relationship
I want to have with you.
Huh?
Even if you and I get together as a couple,
I still want us to compete with
each other, like we always have.
Well, sure, I have fun competing
with you, too, but...
Is that how it's supposed to be
when a guy and a girl go out?
Maybe it's not actually that simple.
But...
I still want to treasure all
the time we've spent together.
You're my childhood friend,
my best bud, my rival, and...
the girl I love.
Is that not good enough?
Your best bud, your rival, and
your girlfriend? What the heck?
But maybe... if it's okay to be that selfish...
Jun!
Jun, I...
love you, too!
Jun!
Hey!
Answer me! You alive?!
Yes!
What?!
(This suspicious behavior is...)
Hey, you know, I'm all mixed up
It's too complicated, I'm freaking out
I want to look cute to you
(crazy, crazy, drive me crazy, and that's…)
So I'm plotting, bargaining,
sly, and stubborn
Dizzying love
Just tell him to look at you
And watch him stiffen up even more,
because you're both so awkward
What? Even if we're alike in that way
It doesn't make me happy, 'cause it
means our love is going nowhere
Cloudy heart, swirling emotions—
I sense rain coming
So I partly open my umbrella,
then sneakily scoot closer to you
Please notice the curl of my
eyelashes as I keep blinking
And don't say I'm acting weird
All this plotting and bargaining
is my sly plan to look cute to you
Try to solve the riddle of
this soft, dizzying love
(Buzzing, fidgeting)
Listen, I might be a bit
tangled in my own web now
But once you unravel the mystery,
you'll see pure lo-love